原作者名：wavywebsurf
视频来源：youtu.be/Bs3jVWiNJRE
原视频发布日期：20190403
字幕翻译/压制：旋火
So if you've been keeping up with the memes in the past few months,
所以如果你在过去几个月里一直在关注这些迷因(梗)的话
you've most likely run into this fellow right here.
你很有可能见过这家伙
Ricardo Milos后文以香蕉君代称
This is Brazilian model and adult entertainment industry worker Ricardo Milos.
这是巴西模特和成〇娱乐业工作者 里卡多米洛斯(香蕉君)
Mr. Ricardo Milos has recently become a meme over on TikTok
香蕉君先生最近在TikTok上成了一个梗
where people take videos of you know these egirl TikTok users
在那里人们使用TikTok有名的福利〇的视频
and place Ricardo Milos dancing in his underwear at the end of their TikTok videos.
并把香蕉君穿着内裤跳舞的部分放在他们的TikTok视频的末尾
That's like this bait-and-switch meme.
就像是引诱与反转的梗
There have been several popular Ricardo Milos meme edit compilations
有几个流行的香蕉君梗大合集视频
that have popped up on YouTube as well.
在油管上也出现了
He's an interesting case because this isn't even the first time Ricardo Milos has been a meme.
这个梗很有趣 因为这甚至不是香蕉君第一次变成梗
He was actually a meme back in 2011 for a completely different reason.
他在2011年的时候就因为完全不同的事情而成为了梗
And we'll talk about that in a bit. Trust me.
我们稍后再谈这个问题 相信我
So it's been pretty funny seeing the rise of the Ricardo Milos memes
所以看到香蕉君梗的兴起是很好玩的
but the source material is pretty old
但素材已经很老了
and there hasn't been any new appearances of Ricardo Milos in the past few years.
而在过去几年里 香蕉君没有任何新的露面
And there's actually a pretty prominent death rumor floating around.
而实际上有一个死亡传闻很有名
This rumor being that Ricardo Milos died sometime in the mid 2010.
这个传闻是说香蕉君在2010年代中期的某个时候去世了
There were many people who were recently fooled by an impostor playing league of legends on Twitch
而最近有很多人被一个在Twitch上玩英雄联盟的冒牌者给骗了
that looks similar to him but this guy isn't the real Ricardo Milos.
这人看起来很像香蕉君 但实际上不是
So today I thought it would be fun to take a look at the origins of the Ricardo Milos meme
那么今天我就来看看香蕉君的起源
and why it became popular again
以及为什么它又开始流行
and also is there any credence to this death rumors surrounding Ricardo Milos.
还有就是香蕉君的死亡传闻是否可信
So Ricardo Milos's presence online goes all the way back to 2004 on his website ricardomilos.net.
那么 香蕉君在网上的存在可以追溯到2004年他的网站ricardomilos.net
The websites no longer available but there is an archived version of it.
网站不再可用 但有一个存档版本
That's pretty easy to find on the internet.
这在网上很容易找到
cv10503
Now I'm not gonna leave a link to it here well
那么我不会在这里附上链接
because I don't want to leave a link in my description box
因为我不想在描述里放这种
that goes directly to you know Not Safe For Work content
直接导向NSFW内容的链接
but I will read an excerpt from the website
但我会从网站上读出一段话
which I think is a great way to introduce who Ricardo Milos is.
我认为这是一个介绍香蕉君的很好的方式
Ricardo Milos, hot Brazilian model and entertainer.
香蕉君 热辣的巴西模特和艺人
Hello. Welcome to the official Ricardo Milos website.
你好 欢迎来到香蕉君的官方网站
Come feel the heat. See my passion and desire, my intensity.
来感受一下热度 看看我的激情和欲望 我的强度(重读)
This site was created for your viewing enjoyment
这个网站的建立是为了让你看得开心
and to have a front-row seat for an intimate view into my life.
以近距离了解我的生活
I am Brazilian and born in Rio de Janeiro with my identical twin brother.
我是巴西人 出生在里约热内卢 和我的双胞胎兄弟一起
I reside now in the United States.
现在我住在美国
I am a professional fitness and adult model, exotic dancer, entertainer
我是一名专业的健身和成〇模特 异国舞者 艺人
and competitive natural bodybuilder.
以及有力的自然健美爱好者
So as you see here, we've got a spicy Brazilian man in Ricardo Milos.
所以 正如你所看到的 这就是火辣的巴西男人 香蕉君
He is truly a jack of all adult industry trades here.
他肯定是成〇行业的老油条了
And there's a lot more on this website than this introduction paragraph
而且这个网站上不仅仅只有这段介绍
but like I said you can find the archive link on the internet pretty easily
但就像我说的 你在网上很容易可以找到存档链接
but I can't show it here cuz my channel would get terminated by YouTube.
但我不能把它放在这里 不然我就会被油管橄榄啦
So with Ricardo properly introduced
那么 香蕉君好好介绍完了
let's get to talking about how he became a meme in late 2010 early 2011 for the first time.
让我们来谈谈他是如何在2010年末2011年初第一次变成梗的吧
Ricardo's first run-in with the memes was
香蕉君第一次变成梗并流行起来
嘎七姆七即Gachimuchi，意为肌肉发达，来源mzh.moegirl.org.cn/哲♂学#光明阵营
when his likeness became popular over on the Gachimuchi community on 2chan.
是在2chan的嘎七姆七社区里
2chan being this website that's actually a predecessor of 4chan
2chan这个网站其实是4chan的前身
but is primarily Japanese speakers on that site.
但在这个网站上的人主要是说日语的
So what the hell is Gachimuchi.
那么嘎七姆七是什么鬼
Gachimuchi was this bizarre meme format
嘎七姆七就是这样奇怪的梗
where users would take video clips of homoerotic wrestling videos
在那里 用户会使用同〇恋摔跤〇情的视频片段
不一定是日本，原作者应该了解不是很深
and splice them together with Japanese imagery and music to create
然后加上日本的图片和音乐来制造出
what I can only consider a mix-up between gay, WWE and anime in these wild video remixes.
我只能认为是同〇恋 世界摔角娱乐和动漫之间的缝合怪
The videos would commonly select clips produced by a handful of actors
这些视频通常会选择一些演员参演的片段进行剪辑
and forum members would also ascribe bios and plot lines to the actors that they used in the edits.
同时相关论坛成员也会在视频中编造演员的简介和剧情
It's honestly one of the most bizarre meme formats that have ever witness.
说实话 这是有史以来最奇葩的梗之一
With that said Ricardo Milos ties into this,
说到这里就得提到了香蕉君
because a video clip of him dancing with the bandana and an American flag thong on
因为他戴着头巾 穿着美国国旗丁〇裤跳舞的视频片段
was pretty popular to be used in these Gachimuchi edits.
被用在这种嘎七姆七剪辑中 是相当受欢迎的
The popularity of Ricardo Milos and the Gachimuchi community spawned several animated parodies
香蕉君和嘎七姆七社区的人气催生了几部动画同人作品
where anime characters were drawn to replicate his iconic American flag thong dance.
其中的动漫人物都在跳他那个标志性的美国国旗丁〇裤舞
It's really hard for me to explain exactly what Gachimuchi is.
对于我来说 真的很难解释清楚什么是哲♂学(嘎七姆七文化)
So I really just have to show you some clips of this though.
所以我真的只能给大家看一些哲♂学视频片段了
[Music]
[音乐]
片段出自哲学♂之巅终极决战（下集）(youtu.be/9rug_NfgjlM)
All right enough Gachimuchi.
好了 足够的嘎七姆七了
Let's get into more familiar territory.
让我们进入更熟悉的领域
Let's talk about how he became a meme on TikTok.
我们来谈谈他是如何成为TikTok上的一个梗的
So the reason why he became a meme more recently on TikTok all stems back to the summer of 2018.
那么 他之所以会在TikTok上成为一个梗 就要追溯到2018年的夏天
It starts on a popular Russian image board similar to 4chan called 2ch.
这要从一个类似于4chan的俄罗斯人气图片网站2ch说起
And despite the similarities of two 2ch to 2chan, the two sites have no association.
而尽管2ch与2chan有相似之处 但这两个网站之间并没有关联
So during the rise of TikTok in 2018, people would go on 2ch in post videos of TikTok girls.
所以在2018年TikTok兴起的时候 人们会在2ch上发布TikTok女性用户的视频
You know making little video remixes or whatever people do on TikTok.
你知道的 就是那种TikTok小视频
You know what I'm saying. I really haven't figured it out yet.
这点我还真没弄明白
But needless to say people on 2ch
但很自然地 2ch的用户
were getting annoyed of people sharing TikTok videos on their (?) forum.
讨厌人们在他们的论坛上分享TikTok视频
So the 2ch users that were getting annoyed started counter spamming with Ricardo Milos's dancing video.
于是那些被惹恼的2ch用户开始用香蕉君的舞蹈视频反击这些垃圾信息
So this resulted in an intense back-and-forth flame/spam war
所以这就导致了一场激烈而愤怒的网络垃圾冲突
between the TikTok posters and the Ricardo Milos posters
这发生在TikTok视频制作者和香蕉君视频制作者之间
until ultimately the whole thing just coalesce into people
直到最后 整件事混合到了一起
putting Ricardo Milos into TikTok videos, editing them in for comedic purposes.
就变成了为了搞笑而把香蕉君放到TikTok视频中
Thus creating the Ricardo Milos bait-and-switch meme that we have now.
因此创造了现在的香蕉君引诱与反转的梗
The popularity of Ricardo Milos over on 2ch would eventually spread over to 4chan
香蕉君在2ch上的受欢迎程度最终就蔓延到了4chan上
and after that Ricardo Milos pretty much became unstoppable and the meme is still in full swing today.
而在那之后 香蕉君几乎变得不可阻挡 而这个梗至今仍在流行
So with the origins of the Ricardo Milos meme explained,
那么香蕉君梗的起源解释完了
let's get into this death rumor that I've been seeing floating around online.
让我们来谈谈这个网上流传的死亡传闻吧
And before you say bro wavy Ricardo Milos is alive,
等下 老哥 在你对我说 香蕉君其实还活着
I saw him streaming League of Legends on Twitch the other day.
前几天我在Twitch上看到他在直播英雄联盟 之前
That's a hundred percent inaccurate and I'm going to explain why.
我得先说下 这肯定不对 我来解释下
On March 3rd Brazilian bodybuilder Nilton Felix
3月3日 巴西健美爱好者尼尔顿菲利克斯
started streaming on Twitch under the username Ricardo Milos LOL.
开始在Twitch上以Ricardo Milos LOL的用户名进行直播
So the guys Twitch channel is Ricardo Milos LOL
所以这家伙的Twitch频道是Ricardo Milos LOL
and if you look at the streamer himself he looks pretty damn similar to Ricardo Milos.
如果你看一下他的长相 确实很像香蕉君
And not only does the guy stream League, he does these dances on stream
而且这家伙不仅是直播英雄联盟 还在直播中跳舞
and I can't lie. It's convincing. This guy looks like Ricardo Milos.
我得承认 这很有说服力 这家伙看起来像香蕉君
And for a while the internet really thought that this guy was Ricardo Milos
有一阵子网络上的人都认为这家伙是香蕉君
and people would start flocking to this new Twitch channel
而人们就开始涌向这个新的Twitch频道
with the guy getting a hundred thousand followers as of today.
而这个家伙现在就得到了十万粉丝
But eventually people would start pointing out differences in his facial features
但最终人们会开始指出他的面部特征的不同之处
and something wasn't adding up about the whole situation.
除此之外 还有一些事情也没法解释
So there were definitely skeptics out there but they were honestly in the right
因此 肯定有人怀疑 但他们其实是对的
because later on the guy would come clean saying that he wasn't Ricardo Milos
因为后来这家伙就坦白说他不是香蕉君
and revealed himself to be a man named Nilton Felix linking his Instagram in his Twitch bio.
并透露自己是尼尔顿菲利克斯 他在他的Twitch介绍中放了他的Instagram链接
So yeah before you start typing don't say that Ricardo Milos isn't dead
所以是的 在你开始打字之前 不要说香蕉君没有死
because you just saw him on Twitch the other week.
说什么因为你前几周刚在Twitch上看到他了
That's not the case. That was an impostor.
这不是一回事 那是个冒牌货
So where does this death rumor actually come from.
那么这个死亡传闻到底是怎么来的呢
During the research for this video I saw people asking the question is Ricardo Milos dead
在做视频的研究过程当中 我看到有人问这个问题 香蕉君死了吗？
and I'm like why the hell do people say this.
我就搞不懂为什么人们会这么说
And I can't really find anything super specific.
我真的找不到这个传闻有什么特别具体的来历
It's just one of those things where someone disappears on the internet for a while
这就像是你在网上消失了一段时间
and people just jump to conclusions and assume that you're dead.
人们就觉得你已经死了
But there is one thing that I found
但有一件事 我发现
that maybe leading people to think that he's dead or got injured somehow.
也许会让人们认为他已经死了 或者是受了什么伤
And that is a post on his Facebook page.
而这是来自他facebook上的一个贴子
The last publicly available post on the official Ricardo Milos Facebook page
香蕉君官方facebook上最后一个公开的贴子
was posted on September 7th of 2017.
是在2017年9月7日发布的
In this post states everyone be safe in the path of Irma.
在这个贴子里 他说 在厄玛的路径上的每个人都要注意安全
Irma of course referring to hurricane Irma which was a category 5 hurricane
当然厄玛指的是五级飓风厄玛
that struck several Caribbean islands and southern Florida
袭击几个加勒比岛屿还有佛罗里达州南部
resulting in a total of a hundred and thirty-four fatalities.
导致总共134人死亡
And Ricardo Milos is indeed based out of Miami Florida
而香蕉君确实是住在佛罗里达州迈阿密附近的
and if he didn't evacuate would have directly been affected by Hurricane Irma.
而如果他不撤离 就会直接受到飓风厄玛的影响
With this being his last post on the Facebook page,
因为这是他在facebook上的最后一个贴子
I can certainly understand where some people would see this
我当然能理解有些人对这一点的看法
and assume oh my god Ricardo Milos got swept away in hurricane Irma.
并认为 哦 我的妈耶 香蕉君被飓风厄玛卷走了
But this can easily be dispelled
但这种说法很容易被证伪
because there is a list of all the fatalities from that hurricane on the internet
因为网上有一份飓风厄玛造成的人员死亡的名单
and Ricardo Milos is nowhere to be seen on that list.
而在名单上根本找不到香蕉君
He doesn't even show up on a casualties list.
他甚至没有出现在伤者名单上
So clearly he wasn't killed by hurricane Irma.
所以很明显他并没有因飓风厄玛而死
But if you look around online it's hard to find any new updates from Ricardo Milos past 2017.
不过你在网上确实很难找到香蕉君在2017年以后的新动态
So I guess he's dead, right?
所以我猜他已经死了 对吗？
Well I found something that may debunk this rumor on a website called bigmuscle.com.
好吧 我在一个叫bigmuscle.com的网站上发现了一些东西 可能会推翻这个传言
经查，香蕉君的账号@HungBrazilian9已经注销
Ricardo Milos has an account on this website
香蕉君在这个网站上有一个账号
and the site itself acts as a listing
而网站本身提供了一个清单
providing information for those who may be interested in working with Ricardo Milos.
为那些可能有兴趣与香蕉君合作的人提供信息
it says the account was created on march 19th of 2004
它说该账号创建于2004年3月19日
which is remarkably close to the time when he launched ricardomilos.net
这与他创办ricardomilos.net的时间非常接近
so this account is definitely legit and owned by Ricardo Milos.
所以这个账号应该就是香蕉君的
It says here it was last updated on August 5th of 2017.
这里说它最后一次更新是在2017年8月5日
But here's the smoking gun.
但这只是个烟雾弹
It says that the account was last accessed on December 19th of 2018
它说这个账号最后一次被访问是在2018年12月19日
so that means that Ricardo Milos has signed into his bigmuscle.com account
所以这意味着香蕉君已经登录到他的bigmuscle.com账号了
as recent as December of last year.
就在去年12月
Sure somebody else could have his account information and log into it
当然 别人可以登录他的账号
but with the account being so obscure and so old,
但因为这个账号如此晦涩 如此古老
I feel like that's a more unlikely situation than Ricardo Milos just logging into the account himself.
我觉得更有可能还是香蕉君自己登录的
What's even more interesting is December of 2018
更有意思的是2018年12月这个时间点
is just around the time when the Ricardo Milos memes started to become popular.
正好是香蕉君的梗开始流行的时候
So what I think happened here is Ricardo Milos found out about the memes being made about him
所以 我认为可能是 香蕉君发现了他的梗
and logged into his social media accounts, checking messages and emails.
并登录他的社交媒体账号来查看信息和电子邮件
So my only conclusion here is that Ricardo Milos as of December of 2018 was definitely alive
所以我在这里唯一的结论是 香蕉君在2018年12月的时候 绝对还活着
and he is most likely aware of the memes being made about him.
而且他还很可能知道关于他的梗
So Ricardo Milos if you're out there if you're watching this video
所以 香蕉君 如果你在那儿看着这个视频的话
根据gachimuchi.fandom.com/wiki/Ricardo_Milos的信息，香蕉君大概是隐退了，不用再找了
and you want a platform to just address the people of the Internet.
而你想要一个平台 只是向大家传达什么话
Hit me up bro. I'm all ears.
可以找我
But to answer the question post in the thumbnail of this video
但要回答这个视频缩略图中的问题
is Ricardo Milos alive.
香蕉君还活着吗？
I think more than likely he is and he's aware of what we're doing here online.
我想他很有可能活着 而且知道我们在网上做的事情
So what did you guys think about this video.
I know you guys have been incessantly requesting me cover Ricardo Milos in the comment section.
I listen and I deliver.
Let me know if you want to hear about next.
Major shoutouts to my patrons.
I appreciate you guys.
Wavywebsurf out.
Peace.
[Music]
[音乐]